Guide to the Sigma Delta Epsilon records, 1920-2012
Sigma Delta Epsilon records, 1920-2012
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Sigma Delta Epsilon records, 1920-2012
3605
Sigma Delta Epsilon.
9.2 cubic feet.
Includes correspondence, bulletins, membership lists, reports, minutes, financial records, questionnaires, records of conventions, and histories, newsletters, and related records, as well as tape recordings.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, bulletins, membership lists, reports, minutes, financial records, questionnaires, records of conventions, and histories of Sigma Delta Epsilon and its chapters, newsletters, and related records. Also, tape recordings of Grand Chapter meeting, National Council meeting, and 65th Anniversary speeches, 1986.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Sigma Delta Epsilon is a sorority for graduate women in science.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, bulletins, membership lists, reports, minutes, financial records, questionnaires, records of conventions, and histories of Sigma Delta Epsilon and its chapters, newsletters, and related records. Also, tape recordings of Grand Chapter meeting, National Council meeting, and 65th Anniversary speeches, 1986.
Charter for the establishment of a chapter at Iowa State College, 1925.
Proclamations for "Women in Science Week," from the Governor of Massachusetts and the Mayor of Boston, June 7-13, 2004.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Sigma Delta Epsilon.; Graduate Women in Science.
Subjects:
Women--Societies and clubs.; Women in science.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. National Council, Minutes and Correspondence
Box 1
Series II. Reports to National Council
Box 2
Series III. Folders on Deceased or Honorary Members, National Newsletters, National Membership Rosters, Minutes of National Meetings
Box 3
Series IV. Histories of Individual Chapters, Minutes of National Meetings
Box 4
Series V. Current and Historical Material
Box 45
Series VI. Copies of Publications, Bulletins and Newsletters
Box 6-9
Series VII. Chapter Meetings
Box 10
Series VIII. Items Added October 1, 1987
Box 10
Series IX. Items Added November 21, 1992
Box 10
Series X. Items Added
Box 12
Series VI. Cassette Tapes
Box 13
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. National Council, Minutes and Correspondence
  - "Personnel - National Council" Lists of national officers 1935/1936 - 1967/1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Personnel of National Committees" Lists of national committees and committee member 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "SDE 1968 National Council Grand Chapter Membership Roster" Reports, list of members by chapter 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "SDE 1968 Grand Chapter Meeting Membership Roster" Reports, lists of members by chapter 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "1968 National Meetings" Includes 3 smaller folders. "SDE 1968 National Council Grand Chapter Membership Roster" Reports, lists of members by chapter 1968; "Sigma Delta Epsilon" Report by auditor 1967/1968; Untitled folder containing reports, questionnaires, correspondence, lists of members in 1968. Loose material includes minutes, reports, lists and agenda for Kansas City meetings (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "1967 Council Meetings" Includes 3 smaller folders, "1967 Grand Chapter Meeting" of reports, minutes, budget, notes 1967; "Sigma Delta Epsilon" Report of auditor 1966/1967; "1967 National Council Meetings" Minutes, reports 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "1966 December National council Meetings" Minutes, reports, budget transcription, lists 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "1966 Grand Chapter Meeting" Budget, minutes, reports, newsletter, pamphlet, notes, photograph 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "1966 National Council and Board of Directors Meetings August 20-21, 1966 ": Correspondence, minutes, list of members, report of accountant. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "National Council and Grand Chapter Meetings, 1965" Minutes, report, notes concerning meeting in 1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "1964 Convention, Montreal" Report by accountant correspondence, sketch (historical), newsletter, minutes, lists, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "1963 Convention, Cleveland, Ohio" Report of accountant, committee reports, notes, minutes, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "1963 Interim Board Meeting" Correspondence, minutes, schedule, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "1962 Convention, Philadelphia, Pa. Photograph, agenda, lists, reports of committees, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "1962 Interim Board Meetings" list of officers, committees, correspondence, questionnaire, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Tea in Denver - AAAS - 1961" Clipping, correspondence, minutes of AAAS council meeting, list of participating members, 1961/1962 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "1961 Convention, Lafayette, Indiana" Correspondence, list of officers and committees, speech, reports, bulletin of American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "1960 Convention, New York, New York" Minutes, lists of officers and committees, reports, correspondence, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "1959 Convention, Chicago, Ill." Minutes, lists of officers and committees, reports, correspondence, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "1958 Convention, Washington D.C." lists of officers and committee members, notes from meeting, minutes, reports, agenda, correspondence, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "1958 Convention, Washington, D. C. MLR File" Correspondence, minutes, schedule, pamphlet on the meeting, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "1957 Convention, Indianapolis, Indiana" Correspondence, reports, minutes, pamphlet, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "1956 Convention - New York, N.Y." Minutes, schedule, correspondence, lists of members 1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "1955 Convention, Minneapolis, Minneapolis" Minutes, correspondence, lists of officers and committees, list of members, 1954/1955 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - "1954 Convention - Gainesville, Florida." Lists of officers, committees, minutes, schedule of meeting, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "1953 Convention - Madison, Wisconsin" Correspondence, minutes, reports, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "1952 Convention - Ithaca, N.Y." Correspondence, minutes, reports, bulletin, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "1951 Convention, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania" Correspondence, list of members attending minutes, reports, 1951/1952 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - "1950 Convention - Cleveland, Ohio" Meeting schedule, minutes, reports, correspondence 1950. Accompanying material contains compiled minutes of conventions to end of 1938, correspondence and reports concerning fellowships, 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - "National Council Meetings Minutes, agenda, correspondence, reports, 1935-1964 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Series II. Reports to National Council
  - "SDE officers" in larger folder. "Officers" Lists, reports of committees; 1959-1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Alpha: Officers and Members" Correspondence, lists of officers and members, questionnaires; 1924-1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Beta: Officers and Members" Correspondence, questionnaires, lists of officers and members; 1922/1923 - 1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Gamma: Officers and Members" Correspondence, questionnaires, lists; 1926 -1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Delta: Officers and Members" Correspondence, questionnaires lists; 1925 -1966/1967 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Epsilon: Officers and Members" Correspondence, questionnaires lists; 1926 -1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Zeta: Officers and Members" Correspondence, lists, questionnaires; 1927 -1948 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Eta: Officers and Members" Correspondence, lists, questionnaires; 1927 -1956 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Theta: Officers and Members" Correspondence, lists, questionnaires; 1928 -1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "Iota: Officers and Members" Correspondence, lists, questionnaires; 1928 -1969 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Kappa: Officers and Members" Correspondence, lists, questionnaires; 1930 -1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Lambda: Officers and Members" Correspondence, lists, questionaires; 1934/1935 -1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "Nu: Officers and Members" Correspondence, lists questionnaires; 1936-1969/1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Xi: Officers and Members" Correspondence, Lists, questionnaires; 1944-1969/1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - "Omicron: Officers and Members" Correspondence, Lists, questionnaires; 1948/1949-1969/1970 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - "Pi: Officers and Members" Correspondence, Lists, questionnaires; 1949-1969/1970 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - "Rho: Officers and Members" Correspondence, Lists, questionnaires; 1954-1967 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - "Sigma: Officers and Members" Correspondence, lists, questionaires; 1954-1967 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - "Tau: Correspondence" Correspondence; 1959-1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - "Tau: Officers and Members" Questionnaires, lists; 1963-1970 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Series III. Folders on Deceased or Honorary Members, National Newsletters, National Membership Rosters, Minutes of National Meetings
  - A. History of S.D.E 1921-1971, 4 notebooks of early history
    - "A History of Sigma Delta Epsilon 1921-1971" (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - History of Sigma Delta Epsilon 1921-1941 (?) (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Sigma Delta Epsilon Graduate Women's Scientific Fraternity The Beginnings (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - History of Sigma Delta Epsilon 1921-1941 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Draft of history of Sigma Delta Epsilon (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - B. Honorary Members - Biographical Folders
    - Dr. Virginia Apgar (Box 3)
    - Dr. Lela V. Barton (Box 3)
    - Dr. Katharine Blodgett (Box 3)
    - Louise A. Boyd (Box 3)
    - Dr. Dr. Mary Bunting (Box 3)
    - Dr. Annie Jump Cannon (Box 3)
    - Dr. Margery Carlson (Box 3)
    - Dr. Emma P. Carr (Box 3)
    - Dr. Cornelia M. Clapp (Box 3)
    - Zada N. Cooper (Box 3)
    - Dr. Irene Corey Diller (Box 3)
    - Dr. Helen Dyer (Box 3)
    - Dr. Sophia Eckerson (Box 3)
    - Dr. Bernice Eddy (Box 3)
    - Alice Evans (Box 3)
    - Dr. Margaret Ferguson (Box 3)
    - Dr. Eloise Gerry (Box 3)
    - Dr. Lillian Moller Gilbreth (Box 3)
    - Winifred Goldring (Box 3)
    - Dr. Esther M. Greisheimer (Box 3)
    - Dr. Alice Hamilton (Box 3)
    - Dr. Helen Hart (Box 3)
    - Dr. Ariel C. Hollinshead (Box 3)
    - Dr. Dorothy Horstmann (Box 3)
    - Dr. Flemmie Kittrell (Box 3)
    - Dr. Rebecca Lancefield (Box 3)
    - Dr. Jane Leichsenring (Box 3)
    - Kathleen Lonsdale (Box 3)
    - Dr. Madge Thurlow Macklin (Box 3)
    - Dr. Mary E. Maver (Box 3)
    - Dr. Elizabeth McCoy (Box 3)
    - Dr. Mary McWhinnie (Box 3)
    - Dr. Margaret Mead (Box 3)
    - Dr. Florence Metz (Box 3)
    - Dr. Katherine Van Winkle Palmer (Box 3)
    - Dr. Helen S. Parsons (Box 3)
    - Dr. Edith Marian Patch (Box 3)
    - Dr. Jeanette Piccard (Box 3)
    - Dr. Margaret Pittman (Box 3)
    - Dr. Edith Quimby (Box 3)
    - Dr. Mina Rees (Box 3)
    - Dr. Mary Elizabeth Reid (Box 3)
    - Dr. May S. Reynolds (Box 3)
    - Dr. Jane Sands Robb (Box 3)
    - Dr. Mary Rogick (Box 3)
    - Dr. Florence Sabin (Box 3)
    - Dr. Florence B. Seibert (Box 3)
    - Dr. Mary L. Sherrill (Box 3)
    - Dr. Maud Slye (Box 3)
    - Dr. Bertha Van Hoosen (Box 3)
    - Dr. Marion E. Webster (Box 3)
    - Dr. Elizabeth K. Weisburger (Box 3)
    - Dr. Anna Pell Wheeler (Box 3)
    - Dr. Anna Rachel Whiting (Box 3)
    - Dr. Frances Wick (Box 3)
    - Dr. Mary Louise Willard (Box 3)
    - Dr. Chien-Shiung Wu (Box 3)
    - Dr. Charlotte M. Young (Box 3)
  - C. Minutes
    - Minutes of Zeta chapter 1925-1947 (2 volumes) (Box 3)
  - D. National Meetings Reports 1968-June 1971
    - 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - June 1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - December 1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - June 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - December 1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - June 1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - December 1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - June 1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - February 1974 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - June 1974 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - January 1975 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - June 1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - February 1976 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - June 1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - February 1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - June 1977 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - February 1978 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - June 1978 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - E. Membership Rosters 1920-1975
    - 1922-1927 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - 1933-1938 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 1955 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - 1958 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - 1967 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - 1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - 1974 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - F. Photographs --- honorary members and presidents. (15 folders)
  - G. National Meetings Reports 1968-June 1971
    - 1922-1928 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - 1929-1937 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 1930-1936 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - 1931-1947 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 1925-1929 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - 1930-1938 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - 1935-1948 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 1950-1961 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Series IV. Histories of Individual Chapters, Minutes of National Meetings
  - H. Histories of Active Chapters
    - 16 Folders: (see listing for chapter names) (Box 5)
  - I. Histories of Inactive Chapters
    - 8 folders (see listing for chapter names) (Box 5)
  - J. Historical Material Compiled for Golden Anniversary History including the program from the event, 1971
    - 1 binder, includes Certificate of Amendment of the Certifcate of Incorporation (Box 5)
  - Grand Chapter Meeting Minutes for January and June Meetings, 1975
    - Includes Constitution and Bylaws
    - (Box 5)
  - Grand Chapter Meeting Minutes for February Meeting, 1976
    - (Box 5)
  - Grand Chapter Meeting Minutes for February and June Meetings, 1977
    - (Box 5)
  - Grand Chapter Meeting Minutes, Chapter Reports and "A History of Sigma Delta Epsilon" edited by Mary Louise Robbins1978
    - Includes Bylaws
    - (Box 5)
  - Grand Chapter Meeting Minutes and program from the June event, 1979
    - 1 binder, 1 folder (Box 5)
    - (Box 5)
- Series V. Current and Historical Material
  - Current Material; 1983-1984
    - Grand Chapter Meeting Kit; May 1984 (Box 6)
    - Honors and Awards to Members; 1982-1984 (Box 6)
    - In Memoriam Edith Seymour Jones; 1896-1984 (Box 6)
  - Historical Material; 1921-1978
    - Secretaries' Notes and Minutes, 1921-1922 and 1927 (Box 6)
    - Pictures and Tributes to Early Members and Charter Members (Box 6)
    - Certificate of Incorporation, June 1926 (Box 6)
    - Membership Lists, 1922-1927 and National Directory, 1927 and 1938 (Box 6)
    - Charter Members 1921 and list of Charter Members living in 1970. (Box 6)
    - Report of Annual Conventions, 1927 and 1933 (Box 6)
    - Fellowship Fund, 1930-1938 (Box 6)
    - Initiation Ceremonies, 1936, other years up to 1975 (Box 6)
    - Early Sigma Delta Epsilon Newsletters, 1923-1945 (Box 6)
    - National Constitutions, 1920s-1967 (Box 6)
    - National Constitutions, 1923, 1926, 1931-1933, 1941 and 1972 (Box 6)
    - Early history to 1942 --Our first 20 years. (Box 6)
    - History of Chapters by Historical Committee 1966 (Lois Fogelsanger, Alpha) (Box 6)
    - Pictures and Program of 50th Anniversary celebration of Founding SDE held June 19, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence (1971) re change of Name (Box 6)
    - Certificate of Amendment, 1971 (Box 6)
    - History of SDE 1972-1978 (Box 6)
    - History of Paleontological Research Institute (1932-1982) by Katherine V.W. Palmer (Box 6)
  - Historical Material continued, 1921-1984
    - Material on the Griswold Memorial Fund at the Cornell University Plantations Established 1984 (Box 7)
    - History of the Paleontological Research Institute (1932-1982) by Katherine V.W. Palmer (clippings included) (Box 7)
    - Meeting Notices Fall 1980 through December 1983 (Box 7)
    - Membership Lists 1978-1984 (Box 7)
    - Chapter Honorary Membership, 1978, Frank H.T. Rhodes (Box 7)
    - Slate of Officers 1964-1966, 1970-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 7)
    - Constitution for Alpha Revised 1973 and 1978 (Box 7)
    - Installation ceremony for officers, duties of officers, and the Badge (Box 7)
    - Federation of Organization for Professional Women (FOPW), 1973 (Box 7)
    - 50th Anniversary Meeting, June 1971 in Ithaca, N.Y. Alpha, Hostess chapter (Box 7)
    - Alpha Newsletters 1964, 1968-1975, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Annual Reports and minutes of Secretary 1969-1971 (Box 7)
    - Regional Meeting, May 1968 (Box 7)
    - 45th Anniversary Pictures, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Brief History of SDE, 1921-1962 (Box 7)
    - Alpha History after 1967 (2 copies) (Box 7)
    - Reactivation Meetings, 1964-1966 (Box 7)
    - Reactivation Correspondence with National and chapters, 1964 and 1965 (Box 7)
    - Initiation Invitation and Banquet Program, 1953 and 1958 (Box 7)
    - Early History: 1921-1942 2nd copy (1st copy in C.U. Archives of National) (Box 7)
    - Early History: Housekeeping and bookkeeping accounts of 1927 War Bond Purchase (1944), SDE House 502 Dryden Road (Box 7)
    - Early Constitutions: Before 1932 Revised 1932 (other copies in C.U. Archives) (Box 7)
    - Laua A. Minns: Certificate of Membership 1921, Memorials to Miss Minns, Her notes on expenses for Dryden Road House (Box 7)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Pictures, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Professional Skills Roster--History, Publicity, Reports 1967-1971 (Box 7)
  - Current Material, continued 1984-1986
    - Grand Chapter Meeting Kits: May 1985 Los Angeles, May 1986 Philadelphia (Box 12)
    - Membership Directory: 1948-1985 (Box 12)
    - History: Brief History 1921-1962 (One page), 1921-1971 (Bound Copy) (Box 12)
    - History: Explanation of SDE Emblem designed by V.Graham, Alpha explanation by M. Ellis, Delta (Box 12)
    - Margery Carleson (1892-1985) Member of SDE and founder of Illinois Chapter of Nature Conservancy, Articles and pictures (Box 12)
    - Alice S. Rossi Article: Women in Science: Why so few? Reprint from Science, May 28, 1965 Vol. 148, No. 3674 Pages 1196-1202 (Box 12)
    - Alice S. Rossi Article: Women Scientists: Problems and Prospects, Paper delivered to conference on Women in Science. The Wisconsin Center, Madison Wisconsin, March 19, 1966 (Box 12)
    - Professional Skills Roster: Articles from Ithaca Journal on Roster Closing, July 12, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Material for National Archives: Received from National Secretary, Ethaline Cortelyou
    - Founding of Alpha Alpha Chapter: Burlington, VermontAugust 4, 1981 (Box 8)
    - Bylaws and Constitutions: 1961, 1964, 1965, 1974, 1975, 1978, 1981 (Box 8)
    - Chapter Officers: 1959, 1973-1974, 1974-1975, 1977-1978, 1979-1980, 1980-1981, 1921-1982, 1982-1983 (Missing 1975-1976, 1976-1977, 1978-1979) (Box 8)
    - Epsilon Chapter--Reactivation 1981 (Box 8)
    - Forms--Samples: Election to affiliate membership, National Honorary Membership (Box 8)
    - Grant-in-aid: Statement of Policy (Box 8)
    - Honorary Members: Recommendations, Nominations and Vitae 1982 & 1986 (Box 8)
    - Honorary Members: Deceased Dr. Shirley Quimby Oct. 7, 1984; Dr. Anna Young Whiting September 25, 1980 (Box 8)
    - Incorporation: Articles of Incorporation 1922, Amendment to Article 1971, Title IX regulation (Box 8)
    - Membership Lists: (In separate bindings) 1966-1968, 1970-1975, 1978-1979, 1979-1980, 1980-1981 (Xi only), 1985 Complete, Some chapter members missing in earlier years. (Box 8)
    - National Office: 1976-1980 Washington, D.C. Procedure Manual, Interoffice memos, hours worked (Box 8)
    - National Officers: of SDE/GWIS listed from 1922-1986 (Box 8)
    - White House Letter: List of Reagan female appointments 1982 (Box 8)
- Series VI. Copies of Publications, Bulletins and Newsletters
  - Sigma Delta Epsilon News
    - Vol. 1, No. 1,2 1935 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 2, No: 1, 2 1936 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 3, No. 1, 2 1937 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 4, No. 1,2 1938 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 5, No. 1,2 1939 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 6, No. 1,2 1940 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 7,No. 1,2 1941 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 8, No. 1,2 1942 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 9, No. 1April 1943 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 9, No. 2 January 1944 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 10, No. 1 May 1944 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 10, No. 2December 1944 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 11, No. 1 June 1945 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 11, No.2 May 1946 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 12, No. 1 December 1947 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 12, No. 2 March 1948 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 13, No. 1 December 1948 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 13, No. 2 1949 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 14, No. 1,2 1950 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 15, No. 1 December 1950 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 15, No. 2 December 1951 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 16, No. 1,2 1952 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 17, No. 1,2 1953 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 18, No. 1 May 1954 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 18, No. 2 May 1955 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 19, No. 1 November 1955 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 19, No. 2 May 1956 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 20, No. 1 November 1956 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 20, No. 2 April 1957 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 21, No. 1 November 1957 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 22, No. 1 May 1958 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 23, No. 1 May 1959 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 2, No. 2 November 1959 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 24, No. 1,2 1960 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 25, No. 1,2 1961 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 26, No. 1,2 1962 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 27, No. 1,2 1963 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 28, No. 1,2 1964 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 29, No. 1,2 1965 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 30, No. 1,2 1966 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 31, No. 1,2,3 1967 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 32, No. 1,2 1968 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 33, No. 1,2 1969 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 34, No. 1,2 1970 (Box 8)
  - Name Changed to Sigma Delta Epsilon Graduate Women in Science BULLETIN
    - Vol. 35, No. 1,2 1971 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 36, No. 1,2 1972 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 37, No. 1,2 1971 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 38, No. 1,2 1971 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 39, No. 1,2 1975 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 40, No. 1,2 1975 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 41, No. 1,3,4 (#2 missing) 1975 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 42, No. 1,2,3,4 1975 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 43, No.3,4 (1 and 2 missing) 1979-1980 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 44, No. 2,3,4 1979-1980 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 45, No. 1,3,4 1979-1980 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 46, No. 1,2,3,4 1982-1983 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 47, No. 1,2,3,4 1982-1983 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 48, No. 1,2,3 1984 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 49, No. 1,2,3,4 1985 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 50, No. 1,2,3,4 1986 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 51, No. 1 1987 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 51, No. 3 Winter 1988 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 51, No. 4 Spring 1988 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 52, No. 1 Summer 1988 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 52, No. 2 Fall 1988 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 52, No. 3 March 1989 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 52, No. 4 May 1989 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 52, No. 5 June 1989 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 53, No. 1 August 1989 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 53, No. 2 October 1989 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 53, No. 3 December 1989 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 53, No. 4 February 1990 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 53, No. 5 April 1990 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 53, No. 6 June 1990 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 54, No. 1 August 1990 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 54, No. 2 October 1990 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 54, No. 3 December 1990 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 54, No. 4 April 1991 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 55, No. 1 1991 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 55, No. 2 December 1991 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 55, No. 3 March 1992 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 55, No. 4 June 1992 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 56, No. 1 August 1992 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 58, No. 2 (numbered thus)January 1993 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 56, No. 1 (numbered thus)October 1993 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 56, No. 2 February 1994 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 56, No. 3 May 1994 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 57, No. 1 September 1994 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 57, No. 2 February 1995 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 57, No. 3 June 1995 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 58, No. 1 Fall 1995 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 58, No. 2 Winter 1996 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 58, No. 3 Spring 1996 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 59, No. 1 Fall 1996 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 59, No. 2 Spring 1997 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 59, No. 3 Summer 1997 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 60, No. 1 Fall 1997 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 60, No. 2 Spring 1998 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 61, No. 1 Fall 1887 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 61, No. 2 Winter 1999 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 61, No. 3 Spring 1999 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 62, No. 1 Fall 1999 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 62, No. 2 Winter 2000 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 62, No. 3 Spring 2000 (Box 8)
    - Vol. 63, No. 1 Fall 2000 (Box 8)